bilerico.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy / LGBTQ Nation

At **LGBTQ Nation** , we understand that your privacy is important to you; it’s important to us also, and that is why we provide this statement about the personal information we collect, how we use that information and with whom it may be shared. You should not, and are not required to, disclose any information that you do not want made public.

**Information We Collect:**

The only personal information that we collect is information you provide when completing your membership profile and updates. We use that information to build your online profile and personalize your experience at our website. Your profile will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal. If you send us correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file, which is only accessed by us or authorized law enforcement officials on demand.

In the course of creating and using your account, we may automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses, and monitor traffic patterns and related use of our Service to help us improve our web pages, site design, and member experience.

**Email Policy**  
How we use and protect your Email Address:

We obtain your email address when you register an account, subscribe to our mailing list, or contact us with an inquiry or letter to the editor.

Your email address is known only to us, and is never published or revealed by us to other users of this site. We make every effort to safeguard you from receiving unsolicited email or spam by safeguarding your email address.

In creating an account with our Service, you have established a business relationship with LGBTQ Nation, and acknowledge that you may, on occasion, receive email communication promoting the features and content of this service. However, we will not sell or rent your email addresses to any third party without your permission.

You should understand that posting your email address in any visible area of our site, or in any comment field, is strongly discouraged, as you are making it publicly available to others to send you unsolicited email.

**Cookies:**

Cookies are used to deliver content specific to a user’s potential interests and for the administration of passwords, among other purposes. For example, we also may use cookies to deliver customized content and/or targeted advertisements and product offerings. It is important to note that cookies are not linked to personal information. Since our website is specifically designed to your interests, disabling your browser from accepting cookies may prevent you from accessing some features on LGBTQ Nation.

**Your IP Address:**

Your IP address is commonly used by most websites to collect demographic data, track site usage and improve service. Whenever possible, we collect your IP address when you visit our site, the search criteria or referring website you visited prior, and information such as your operating system, browser, screen resolution settings, your internet service provider, your city (or country) of origin, pages viewed, and frequency and length of visits to our site. We automatically gather this information and translate the data into a resource that we can use to identify and correct problems with our website, better understand our users and their preferences for different offerings on our site, and to continually update and expand our service.

**Discussion Threads, Public Comments:**

If you use a group discussion thread, post a public comment, or participate in any live interaction with other users, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.

We are not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums. It is important for you to exercise discretion and appropriate caution when deciding, if at all, to reveal Personal Information in these areas. Users who violate Community Standards, our Terms of Service, or any other policy may be temporarily or permanently banned from accessing this website at any time, according to our sole discretion.

**Third Party Collections of Information:**

LGBTQ Nation has no control over any persons, third party web sites, links or email addresses posted to this website. We do not screen landing pages of external links, and assume no responsibility for any web navigation, including links to members’ personal websites or blogs, or textual or banner advertisements, that takes you off this site, and that is not under our control.

**Third Party Ads**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  Look for the AdChoices logo on certain ads and click it to opt-out of these practices. If you would like to opt-out of third-party advertising, each of the following programs provides an opt-out feature where consumers can choose not to receive targeted advertising from their affiliates: [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) opt out](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) opt out](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). If you are located in the European Union, you may prefer to use the [EDAA opt out](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Because these third parties opt-out is cookie-based, your browser must be set to accept third-party cookies. If you use multiple devices or browsers, you’ll have to opt out on each. If you delete the opt-out cookie, you will need to opt-out again.

**Liability:**

LGBTQ Nation disclaims all liability, regardless of the form of action, for the acts or omissions or claims of other members or users (including unauthorized users, or “hackers”) of our site or services.  
**  
Ownership:**

We reserve the right to transfer ownership of all private and non-private information collected from the use of this website to parties who purchase interest, partnership or ownership of this Service.

**Change in Privacy Statement:**

LGBTQ Nation reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to anyone.

**Mailing Address:**  
LGBTQ Nation, 584 Castro St. #623, San Francisco, CA 94114
